Guide to the Health Systems Agency of Southwestern Pennsylvania Records, 1971-1987 AIS.1987.02
ULS Archives & Special Collections
- Projects, 1971-1987; I.
  - 819-Newton Care Centers--Purchase of Mountain View Nursing Home, 1979 (Box 151)
  - 820-McKeesport Hospital--Family Practice Residency Program Grant Application, 1979
  - 821-Presbyterian-University Hospital--Stereotactic Surgery Center, 1980
  - 822-Monroeville Manor--240 Bed LTC Facility, 1980
  - 823-Centerville Clinics--Rural Health Initiative Continuation Grant Application, 1980
  - 824-St. Francis General Hospital-Community Mental Health Center--Adolescent and Children's Staffing Continuation, 1979
  - 825-John J. Kane Hospital--Replace Obsolete Bed Frames and Mattresses, 1979
  - 826-Medical Center of Beaver County--CT Scanner, 1979
  - 827-Neighborhood Comprehensive Health Services--Primary Health Care Grant Application, 1980
  - 828-Butler County Commissioner's Council on Drugs and Alcohol--Tertiary Program for Female Alcoholics Continuation Grant Application, 1980 (Box 152)
  - 829-Medical Center of Beaver County--Graduate Training in Family Medicine Grant Application, 1980
  - 830-Frienship Village--New 60 LTC Bed Nursing Home and ILU, 1980
  - 831-Magee-Women's Hospitall--Additions and Alterations, 1980
  - 832-Allegheny County Health Department--Immunization Project Continuation Grant Application, 1979
  - 833-Westmoreland Hospital Association--Computer System, 1980
  - 834-Friendship Villa--Purchase of South Hills Convalescent Center, 1979 (Box 153)
  - 835-Sunnyview Home--Program for Replacement, 1979
  - 836-Washington Hospital--Computerized Medical Information System, 1979
  - 837-Uniontown Hospital Association--Renovate Radiology Department, 1980
  - 838-Laurel Manor Village--80 Bed LTC Facility, 1980
  - 839-Sewickley Valley Hospital--Renovation/Modernization Project, 1980 (Box 154)
  - 840-Pennsylvania Department of Health--Venereal Disease Control Continuation Grant, 1980
  - 841-Forbes Health Maintenance Plan--Supplemental Initial Development Proposal for a Qualified HMO Grant Application, 1980
  - 842-Pennsylvania Department of Health--Immunization and Measles Eradication Program Continuation Grant Application, 1979
  - 843-Citizens General Hospital--Replacement of Radiographic-Fluoroscopic Equipment, 1979
  - 844-John J. Kane Hospital--Decentralized Long Term Care Facilities, 1980
  - 845-Children's Hospital--Property Purchase for a Courtyard, 1979
  - 846-Children's Hospital--Property Purchase, 1980 (Box 155)
  - 847-Community Health Clinic--Adolescent Pregnancy Prevention and Services Program Grant Application, 1980
  - 848-Presbyterian-University Hospital--Expansion of Ultrasound Radiology, 1980
  - 849-Miners Clinic--Supplemental Manpower Application to N.H.S.C., 1980
  - 850-McKeesport Hospital--HMO Feasibility Study Grant Application, 1980
  - 851-Tri-State Council on Alcoholism--Detoxification Facility, 1980
  - 852-Mercy Hospital--Solar Energy Demonstration Project, 1980
  - 853-Allegheny County Health Department--Rodent Control/Neighborhood Improvement Continuation Grant Application, 1980
  - 854-Green County Memorial Hospital--Replace Diagnostic Radiology Equipment, 1980
  - 855-Pittsburgh Lifetime Care Community-Sherwood Oaks--58 Skilled Beds, 1980
  - 856-Irene Stacy Community Mental Health Center--Federal Staffing Continuation Grant Application, 1980
  - 857-Southern Indiana Medical Center--Black Lung Clinics Program Grant Application, 1980
  - 858-Armstrong County Memorial Hospital--Replacement of One Tomographic Unit and Three Radiographic Fluoroscopic Units, 1980
  - 859-Centerville Clinics--Black Lung Treatment and Nursing Centers Grant Application, 1980
  - 860-Kiski Armstrong Home Care of Pennsylvania--Black Lung Program Grant, 1980
  - 861-Miners Clinic--Pennsylvania Coal Workers' Respiratory Disease Program Application, 1980
  - 862-Centerville Clinics--Community Mental Health Centers Federal Staffing and Construction Continuation Grant Application, 1980
  - 863-Miners Clinic--Pennsylvania Coal Workers' Respiratory Disease Program Grant Application, 1980
  - 864-University Health Center of Pittsburgh--Replacement of Central Laundry Equipment, 1980
  - 865-Community College of Beaver County--Action-Oriented Continuing Education for Nurses Grant Application, 1980
  - 866-Westmoreland Home Health Care Agency--Black Lung Clinics Program Grant Application, 1980
  - 867-Southern Indiana Medical Center--Federal R.H.I. Continuation Grant Application, 1980
  - 868-St. Barnabas Nursing Home--Renovations Converting Administrative Office Area into an 8 Bed Skilled Care Unit, 1980
  - 869-South Hills Health System Home Health Agency--Respiratory Therapy Service in Home Care Supplemental Grant Application, 1980 (Box 156)
  - 870-Westmoreland Hospital Association Community Mental Health Center--Initial Consultation and Education Grant Application, 1980
  - 871-St. Johns Lutheran Home--Addition of 21 LTC Beds, 1980
  - 872-St. Francis General Hospital--Energy Conservation Measure Program Grant Application, 1980
  - 873-Butler County Commissioners Council on Drugs and Alcohol--Tertiary Program for Female Alcoholics Renewal Grant Application, 1980
  - 874-F.O.R. Sto-Rox Neighborhood Corporation--Urban Health Initiative Continuation Grant Application, 1980
  - 875-Allegheny Valley School--Conversion of 22 Bed Residential Facility to 15 Bed ICF/MR, 1980
  - 876-Centerville Clinics--HMO Feasibility Study Grant Application, 1980
  - 877-Human Services Center-Community Mental Health Centers--Initial Operations Grant Application, 1980
  - 878-Allegheny County Health Department--Fluoridation Project Grant Application, 1980
  - 879-Beaver County Drug and Alcohol Commission--State-wide Services Contract Funds, 1980
  - 880-Mid-Allegheny Clarion Valley Regional Health System--RHI Continuation Grant Application, 1980
  - 881-Westmoreland County Emergency Medical Services Council--Advanced Life Support Training for the Kiski Valley, 1980
  - 882-Community College of Allegheny County--Training of Emergency Medical Technicians/Ambulance Attendants, 1980
  - 883-Westmoreland Hospital Community Mental Health Center--Continuation Operational Grant Application, 1980
  - 884-Allegheny East Mental Health/Mental Retardation Centers--Community Mental Health Center Comprehensive Services Support Renewal Grant Application, 1980 (Box 157)
  - 885-Emergency Medical Service Institute--Expansion and Improvement of an Emergency Medical Services System
  - 886-St. Clair Hospital--Energy Conservation Project, 1980
  - 887-Miners Clinics--Rural Health Initiative Continuation Grant Application, 1980
  - 888-Alle-Kiski Health Plan--HMO Planning Grant Application, 1980
  - 889-Passavant Health Center--Facility Expansion, 1980
  - 890-Pittsburgh Lifetime Care Community--Sherwood Oaks, 1980 (Box 158)
  - 891-St. Francis General Hospital--Mobile Radioisotope Camera, 1980
  - 892-Family Planning Council of Western Pennsylvania--Family Planning Services Continuation Grant Application, 1980
  - 893-C. Howard Marcy State Hospital--Life Safety Code Renovations, 1980
  - 894-Skilled Health Facilities--Purchase Assets of Golfview Manor Nursing Home, 1980
  - 895-Skilled Health Facilities--Purchase Assets of Suburban Manor Nursing Home, 1980
  - 896-Presbyterian-University Hospital--Expand Nuclear Cardiology Program, 1980
  - 897-Sewickley Valley Hospital--Energy Management Plan, 1980
  - 898-Western Center--Medical Assistance Compliance, 1980
  - 899-Ellwood City Hospital--Acquisition of Ultra-Sound Scanning Equipment, 1980
  - 900-Presbyterian-University Hospital--Energy Conservation, 1980
  - 901-Pennsylvania Department of Health--High Blood Pressure Control Program, 1980
  - 902-not present
  - 903-Montefiore Hospital--Energy Conservation, 1980
  - 904-Shadyside Hospital--Total Energy Plant, Replacement of Inoperable Equipment and Related Corrective Maintenance, 1980
  - 905-Greene County Memorial Hospital--Adolescent Pregnancy Prevention and Services Grant Application, 1980 (Box 159)
  - 906-C. Howard Marcy State Hospital--Medical Assistance Compliance, 1980
  - 907-C. Howard Marcy State Hospital--Renovations, 1980
  - 908-Centerville Clinics-Rural Health Initiative, 1980
  - 909-Sickle Cell Society of Western Pennsylvania--Screening and Education Clinic, 1980
  - 910-Children's Hospital of Pittsburgh--Equipment for Central Chemistry Lab, 1980
  - 911-Emergency Medical Service Institute --Communication Improvement Project, 1980
  - 912-Lancer Development Corporation--Custodial Care Facility, 1980
  - 913-Allegheny East Mental Health/Mental Retardation Center-Wilkinsburg Facility--Renovations, 1980
  - 914-Sisters of Mercy--HMO Grant Application, 1980
  - 915-McKeesport Hospital--Linear Accelerator, 1980
  - 916-Health and Welfare Planning Association--Health Risk Reduction at the Worksite, 1980
  - 917-Mercy Hospital of Pittsburgh--Energy Conservation Measures Program, 1980
  - 918-Department of Health--Migrant Health Program, 1980
  - 919-Indiana County Head Start--Maternal Infant Child Care Project, 1980
  - 920-College Misericordia--Home Health Service Training Grant, 1980
  - 921-Allegheny Valley Hospital--Replacement and Renovation of Building, 1980 (Box 160)
  - 922-Pennsylvania Department of Health--Genetic Disease Testing and Counseling Services Program, 1980
  - 923-Henry Clay Frick Community Hospital--Refinancing of Bond Issue, 1980
  - 924-Newton Care Centers--Renovation and Addition of Beds at Mountain View Nursing Home, 1980
  - 925-Armstrong County Memorial Hospital--Addition of an Operating Room, 1980
  - 926-Dexter K. Case--Renovate and Add 100 New Beds, 1980 (Box 161)
  - 927-Sewickley Valley Hospital--Addition of Psychiatric Beds and Relocation of Psychiatric Unit, 1980
  - 928-Fair Winds Manor--Life Safety Code Renovation, 1980
  - 929-Shadyside Hospital--Pathology Laboratory and Data Processing Department, 1980
  - 930-Westmoreland Hospital Association--Modernization and Expansion, 1980 (Box 162)
  - 931-Jeannette District Memorial Hospital--Medical Office Building, 1980
  - 932-Pennsylvania Department of Health--Diabetes Control Project, 1980
  - 933-Allegheny General Hospital--CAT Scanner, 1980
  - 934-Community Mental Health--Early Childhood Planning Program, 1980
  - 935-St. Francis General Hospital--Developmental Evaluative Services for Children Grant Application, 1980
  - 936-Valley Special Needs Program--ARC Child Development Program, 1980
  - 937-St. Francis General Hospital--Parent-Infant Programs, 1980
  - 938-Community Mental Health Center of Beaver County--Consultation and Education Grant Application, 1980
  - 939-Friends United for Neighborhood Development--Friends United Center Health Services, 1980
  - 940-St. Francis General Hospital--Consultation and Education Services Grant Application, 1980
  - 941-Pennsylvania Department of Health--Health Education-Risk Reduction Program, 1980
  - 942-The West End Health Center--Urban Health Initiative Grant Application, 1980 (Box 163)
  - 943-Southeastern Greene Community Health Center--Rural Health Initiative Grant Application, 1980
  - 944-Family Planning Council of Western Pennsylvania--Local Decision Making for Adolescent Reproductive Health Care Programs Grant Application, 1980
  - 945-Family Planning Council of Western Pennsylvania--Family Planning Staff Training in Counseling Skills with Emphasis on Adolescents, 1980
  - 946-Centerville Clinics--Greene County Black Lung Nursing Treatment and Outreach Center, 1980
  - 947-Laurel Health Maintenance Organization--HMO Feasibility, 1980
  - 948-Community Mental Health Center of Armstrong and Indiana Counties--Initial Operations, 1980
  - 949-Community Medical Center of Northwestern Washington County--Health Service Development Project, 1980
  - 950-Allegheny County Health Department--Women, Infant, Child Nutrition Services, 1980
  - 951-South Hills Health System--CT Scanner, 1980
  - 952-Mon Valley Community Mental Health Center--Comprehensive Services Support Program, 1980
  - 953-University of Pittsburgh--Minimizing Alcohol Problems and Smoking Among Youth, 1980
  - 954-Health and Welfare Planning Association--Cooperative High Risk Reduction Program, 1980
  - 955-Beaver Valley Geriatric Center--Bond Refinancing, 1980 (Box 164)
  - 956-St. Clair Hospital--Lease of Automated Differential System, 1980
  - 957-Turtle Creek Valley Mental Health/Mental Retardation--Second Year Initial Operations, 1980
  - 958-West End Health Center--Assignment of Health Manpower by the National Health Service Corps., 1980
  - 959-Henry Clay Frick Community Hospital--Acquisition of Diagnostic Ultrasound Equipment, 1980
  - 960-Pennsylvania Department of Health--Improved Pregnancy Outcome for Pennsylvania, 1980
  - 961-South Hills Health System--Consultation and Education Services Grant Application, 1980
  - 962-South Hills Health System--Respiratory Therapy in Home Care, 1980
  - 963-Point Marion Borough--Water Fluoridation Project, 1980
  - 964-Primary Care Health Services-Alma Illery Medical Center--Health Services Development Grant, 1980
  - 965-Canonsburg General Hospital--Crossroads Medical Coal Workers' Respiratory Disease Program, 1980
  - 966-Allegheny Valley Hospital--Construction of a new 450 Car Parking Garage, 1980
  - 967-United Mental Health, Inc.-- My House Grant Application, 1980
  - 968-Southwestern Pennsylvania Economic Development District--Human Resources Development Program, 1980
  - 969-Southern Indiana Medical Center--Black Lung Clinic Program, 1980
  - 970-South Hills Health System--Renovation and Expansion of 1924 Building, 1980
  - 971-Beaver Valley Geriatric Center--Sale of Facility, 1980
  - 972-Westmoreland Home Health Care Agency--Black Lung Clinic Program, 1980 (Box 165)
  - 973-Friendship Villa--Purchase of Ivy Nursing Home, 1980
  - 974-Citizens General Hospital and Allegheny Valley Hospital--Joint Proposal for a full body CT Scanner, 1980
  - 975-West Greene Health Services--National Health Service Corps Manpower Application, 1980
  - 976-South Hills Health System--Renovation to Remove Architectural Barriers for the Handicapped, 1980
  - 977-Presbyterian-University Hospital--Land Purchase, 1980
  - 978-Forbes Health System--Purchase 8 Acres of Land, 1980
  - 979-Shadyside Hospital--Installation of a New Elevator and Modification of Existing Elevator, 1980
  - 980-Elsie Miller Convalescent Home--Facility Purchase, 1980
  - 981-St. Francis General Hospital--Call Classifier, 1980
  - 982-not present
  - 983-Presbyterian-University Hospital--Construct a Multi-Level Parking Garage, 1980
  - 984-Presbyterian-University Hospital--Parking Garage Expansion, 1980
  - 985-Presbyterian-University Hospital--Replacement of Myelography Radiology Room, 1980
  - 986-Pennsylvania Department of Health--Comprehensive Public Health Services Formula Grant, Tuberculosis Control in Pennsylvania Grant Application, 1980 (Box 166)
  - 987-Allegheny County Health Department--Supplemental Fluoridation Project, 1980
  - 988-Allegheny County Health Department--Childhood Lead Based Paint Poisoning Prevention Program, 1980
  - 989-Children's Hospital--Renovation and Expansion of Office Space at Children's Hospital, 1980
  - 990-Eye and Ear Hospital--Replacement Facility, 1980
  - 991-Saint Anne Home for the Elderly--Construction of Laundry and Maintenance Building, 1980
  - 992-Western Psychiatric Institute and Clinic, Specialty Services Project, Addition of 37 beds, 1980-1981
  - 993-Children's Hospital--Modernization and Expansion Project, 1980 (Box 167)
  - 994-University Health Center--Lothrop/Darragh Parking Garage, 1980
  - 995-Forbes Health System--Renovation of Columbia Health Center, 1980
  - 996-Medical Center of Beaver County--Graduate Training in Family Medicine, 1980
  - 997-University of Pittsburgh--Area Health Education Center Program, 1980
  - 998-University Health Center of Pittsburgh--Renovation of Radiology Department, 1980 (Box 168)
  - 999-Shadyside Hospital--Replace Tomography Unit, 1980
  - 1000-Westmoreland Hospital Association--Energy Conservation Measure, 1980
  - 1001-Divine Providence Hospital--Development of Ultrasound Diagnostic Capability, 1980
  - 1002-Divine Providence Hospital--Energy Conservation, 1980
  - 1003-Centerville Clinics--Rural Health Initiative Grant, 1980
  - 1004-Allegheny Valley Hospital--CT Scanner, 1980
  - 1005-Leader Nursing Centers--180-Bed Nursing Home Facility in Westmoreland County, 1980
  - 1006-Sewickley Valley Hospital--On-line Data Communications and Information System, 1980
  - 1007-North Hills Passavant Hospital--Replacement and Improvement of Radiology Department, 1980
  - 1008-Washington-Greene Prevention Corporation--Fetal Alcohol Syndrome and Alcohol Related Birth Defects, 1980
  - 1009-Commonwealth of Pennsylvania--Health Program for Refugees, 1980
  - 1010-Medical Center of Beaver County--Computerized Laboratory Management System, 1980
  - 1011-Leonard E. Price--Stone Hedge Manor, 1980 (Box 169)
  - 1012-South Hills Health System--Chemistry Clinical Analyzer, 1980
  - 1013-John D. Pippin--Ambulatory Surgical Facility, 1980
  - 1014-Emergency Hall Nursing Home--Kitchen Expansion and Modernization, 1980
  - 1015-Braddock General Hospital--Upgrading Alcoholic Rehabilitation Service, 1980
  - 1016-Baptist Home--Replace Existing Kitchen Facilities, 1980
  - 1017-Monongahela Valley Hospital--Construct LTC Facility, 1980
  - 1018-Grandview Health Center--120-Bed SNF/ICF Facility, 1980
  - 1019-Leader Nursing Centers--180-Bed Nursing Home, 1980
  - 1020-South Hills Health System--Laundry and Support Service Facilities, 1980 (Box 170)
  - 1021-Washington County Health Center--Addition of 250 LTC Beds, 1980
  - 1022-Brownsville General Hospital--Replacement of X-Ray Equipment, 1980
  - 1023-Presbyterian Association for Care of the Aged and Orphans, 1980
  - 1024-Suburban General Hospital--Install and Rent Computerized Information System, 1980
  - 1025-Medical Center of Beaver County--Acquisition of a Telephone System, 1980
  - 1026-Westmoreland Hospital Association--Replace Nuclear Medicine Equipment, 1980
  - 1027-Medical Center of Beaver County--Family Practice Center Renovation, 1980
  - 1028-Medical Center of Beaver County--Replacement of Basic Radiology Equipment, 1980
  - 1029-Bartley J. Morrow, D.D.S.--New Nursing Facility in Beaver County, 1980
  - 1030-Presbyterian-University Hospital--Renovation of Office Space, 1980
  - 1031-Presbyterian-University Hospital--Central Sterile Renovation
  - 1032-University Health Center of Pittsburgh-Joint Radiation Oncology Center--Expansion, 1980 (Box 171)
  - 1033-Montefiore Hospital--Replace Body Scanner, 1980
  - 1034-Weirton Convalescent Center--Construct Nursing Home for Elderly in Washington County, 1980
  - 1035-Regency Hall Nursing Home--Re-Licensing of 21 LTC Beds, 1980
  - 1036-John J. Kane Hospital--Replace Obsolete Bed Frames and Mattresses, 1980
  - 1037-The Horizon Center--Drug and Alcohol Abuse, 1980
  - 1038-Butler County Memorial Hospital--Rehabilitate Primary Electrical Distribution Facility, 1980
  - 1039-Butler County Memorial Hospital--Replace Computer System, 1980
  - 1040-St. Francis General Hospital--Adolescent and Children's Mental Health Staffing Grant Application, 1980
  - 1041-Magee-Womens Hospital--Energy Conservation, 1980
  - 1042-Allegheny County Health Department--Immunization Project, 1980
  - 1043-Pennigan Investment--Long-Term Care Facility in Beaver County, 1980
  - 1044-Fayette County Council for Family Abuse and Human Intervention--Alcoholism Treatment and Rehabilitation Grant Application, 1980
  - 1045-Chicora Medical Center--38 Bed Addition, 1980
  - 1046-St. Clair Memorial Hospital--Acquisition of a CT Scanner, 1980 (Box 172)
  - 1047-St. Johns General Hospital--New Hospital Construction, New Services and 422 Beds, 1980
  - 1048-Commonwealth of Pennsylvania--Immunization and Measles Elimination, 1980
  - 1049-Commonwealth of Pennsylvania--Venereal Disease Control, 1980
  - 1050-Alma Illery Medical Center-Primary Care Health Services--Satellite Clinics-West End Health Center and St. Clair, 1980
  - 1051-Bon Care--Cost Increase, 1980
  - 1052-Community College of Allegheny County--Physician Assistant Training Program, 1980
  - 1053-Northwest Pennsylvania Regional Planning and Development Commission--Emergency Communications System, 1980
  - 1054-Irene Stacy Community Mental Health Center--Continuation Staffing Grant, 1980
  - 1055-Allegheny Valley School--Construction of Five 8-Bed Intermediate Care Facilities, 1980 (Box 173)
  - 1056-Shadyside Hospital--Construction of Office Building, 1980
  - 1057-Allegheny Valley School--Construction of Four 8-Bed Intermediate Care Facilities, 1980
  - 1058-Beaver County Health Care--120-Bed Long Term Care Facility in Brighton Township, 1980
  - 1059-Wesley Manor Home Health Care Center--Cost Increase, 1980
  - 1060-Washington County Council on Alcoholism and Drug Abuse--Crisis Intervention, 1980
  - 1061-Southeastern Greene Community Health Center--Assignment of Two National Health Service Corps Physicians, 1980
  - 1062-Allegheny County Health Department--Rodent Control/Neighborhood Improvement, 1980
  - 1063-Centerville Clinics--Community Mental Health Center, 1980
  - 1064-Citizens General Hospital--Computerized Telephone System, 1980
  - 1065-North Central Pennsylvania Regional Planning and Development Commissions--Rural Health Initiative, 1981
  - 1066-Mid Allegheny Clarion Valley Regional Health System--Rural Health Initiative, 1981 (Box 174)
  - 1067-South Hills Health System-Governor's Council on Drug and Alcohol Abuse--Funding of Women's Prevention Project, 1981
  - 1068-Sto-Rox Neighborhood Family Health Council--Urban Health Initiative, 1981
  - 1069-Dialysis Clinics--Establishment of 13 Station Dialysis Facility in McKeesport, PA, 1981
  - 1070-Family Planning Council of Western Pennsylvania--Application for Continuation Grant, 1981
  - 1071-University of Pittsburgh School of Nursing--Primary Care Nursing of Infant and Children, 1981
  - 1072-Miners Clinics--Rural Health Initiative, 1980
  - 1073-Westmoreland Hospital Association--Community Mental Health Center, 1981
  - 1074-Montefiore Hospital, 6 MeV Linear Accelerator, 1981-1982
  - 1075-Alle-Kiski Valley Health Plan--HMO Initial Development Grant, 1981
  - 1076-Shadyside Hospital--Cost Increase, 1981 (Box 175)
  - 1077-Marian Manor--Renovation of Kitchen and Addition of Recreation Room, 1981
  - 1078-Allegheny East Mental Health/Mental Retardation Center--C.M.H.C. Comprehensive Services Support Renewal Grant, 1981
  - 1079-Sickle Cell Society--Screening, Counseling and Education Continuation Grant Application, 1981
  - 1080-St. Francis General Hospital--Cost Increase, 1981
  - 1081-Presbyterian Home--New 120-Bed LTC Facility in Indiana, 1981
  - 1082-Pennsylvania Department of Health--Pennsylvania Black Lung Clinics Program, 1981
  - 1083-St. Francis General Hospital--Replacement of 27 Patients Monitors, 1981
  - 1084-Allegheny County Health Department--Tuberculosis Control, 1981
  - 1085-St. Francis General Hospital--Cost Increase, 1981
  - 1086-Community College of Allegheny County--Satellite Nursing Program at the Boyce Campus, 1981
  - 1087-Fair Winds Manor--Cost Increase, 1981
  - 1088-Mercy Hospital--Upgrade Special Procedures Radiographic Room, 1981
  - 1089-Pennsylvania Department of Health--Contract with Children's Hospital to Provide Care to Handicapped Children, 1981
  - 1090-Greene County Memorial Hospital--Home Health Services, 1981
  - 1091-Reformed Presbyterian Home--New Long Term Care Facility, 1981
  - 1092-Valley Care Association--120-Bed LTC Facility, 1981 (Box 176)
  - 1093-Community Dialysis Centers--13-Station Hemodialysis Clinic in New Kensington, 1981
  - 1094-Torrance State Hospital--Handicapped Standards Improvements, 1981